JAROL RIERA | FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

571-6598337 | jarolr.webdev@gmail.com | jarolriera.com | linkedin.com/in/jarol-riera/

SUMMARY

Highly motivated and capable Front End Web Developer with over 2 years of experience. Throughout the course of my career, I have gained the necessary experience and perfected my ability to create, maintain and update modern and accessible web interfaces. With a strong technical knowledge and a problem-solving mindset, I have the ability to deliver exceptional results. I am a passionate and dedicated team player, committed to delivering high-quality work and continuously striving to improve my skills and knowledge, this qualities make me a valuable asset to any team.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

✓ JavaScript

TypeScript

React.js

Angular

Bootstrap

SASS

WordPress

Git

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Freelance (May 2021 - Current) | Frontend Web Developer

- Built and maintained websites for clients through various online platforms
- Created guides to document the processes and maintain business continuity

Alsaid Foundation (Aug 2022 - Dec 2022) | Frontend Web Developer Intern

- Meeting with development team to discuss the project requirements & workflow
- Re-designed and developed new updated website for the organization: https://alsaidfoundation.org/

Brainnest (Jun - Aug 2022) | Front End Web Developer Trainee

- Working on business cases based on current or past projects
- Write clean and maintainable code following best practices and standards

EDUCATION

Edx by MIT & Harvard University (Apr - Aug 2021) | Computer science

Frontend Web Developer program. Five course certification.

Liceo Artistico di Brera (Sep 2008 - Jun 2012) | School of Fina Arts

High School diploma - Milan, Italy

PROJECTS

- Koffee E-Commerce: https://dazzling-piroshki-f56cb2.netlify.app/ (Angular)
- iStream Entertainment: https://phenomenal-kulfi-f493f3.netlify.app/ (Angular)
- TodoApp CRUD: https://ornate-klepon-4130d2.netlify.app/ (React.js)

More of my work can be found on my GitHub: https://github.com/jarolthecoder